w, h, wh, wh
w   h   wh   wh
wh, wh, wh
wh   wh   wh
wh, wh, wh.
w, h, wh, wh
w   h   wh   wh
wh, wh, wh
wh   wh   wh
What, what, what!
什么   什么   什么
White, white, white!
白色的   白色的   白色的
What a sweet
多么可爱的一只
little white mouse!
小白鼠
What, what, what!
什么   什么   什么
White, white, white!
白色的   白色的   白色的
What a sweet
多么可爱的一只
little white mouse!
小白鼠
wh, eel, wheel
wh   eel   车轮
wheel, wheel, wheel.
车轮   车轮   车轮
The wheels go round and round.
车轮旋转着
wh, eel, wheel.
wh   eel   车轮
wheel, wheel, wheel.
车轮   车轮   车轮
The wheels go round and round.
车轮旋转着
wh, eat, wheat.
wh   eat   小麦
Wheat, wheat, wheat.
小麦   小麦   小麦
We plant wheat and eat meat.
我们种小麦   吃肉
wh, eat, wheat.
wh   eat   小麦
wheat, wheat, wheat.
小麦   小麦   小麦
We plant wheat and eat meat.
我们种小麦   吃肉
wh, en, when.
wh   en   什么时候
when, when, when.
什么时候   什么时候   什么时候
When are you going to catch the hen?
你什么时候去抓母鸡
wh, en, when.
wh   en   什么时候
when, when, when.
什么时候   什么时候   什么时候
When are you going to catch the hen?
你什么时候去抓母鸡
wh, ich, which.
wh   ich   which
which, which, which.
哪一个   哪一个   哪一个
Which hat belongs to the witch?
哪个帽子是女巫的
wh, ich, which
wh   ich   which
which, which, which
哪一个   哪一个   哪一个
Which hat belongs to the witch?
哪个帽子是女巫的