Lele, I’m so excited to see the animals at the zoo today.
Me, too, Kuan!
At the zoo, we can see that different animals live on different kinds of land and water.
Bats are land animals. They live in caves.
Cool.
Oh, these are camels. I really like camels.
I like them, too. Camels live on land…in the desert.
Pandas also live on land, but they live in forests.
I love pandas. They are so big!
I also love them. Pandas are my favorite animal.
This is an octopus. It lives in the sea.
Hmm, I don’t like the octopus. It’s ugly.
Really? I like it.
These are swans. They live on land and on lakes.
They also fly in the sky.
I think I like swans.
Me, too!
Butterflies also live on the land and fly in the sky.
I like them because they are pretty.
Yeah, I also like them.
Ooh, and these are dinosaurs…I love dinosaurs!
Most dinosaurs lived only on land, but some dinosaurs lived in the sea,
and some could fly in the sky, right?
Right. I hate them, though. Dinosaurs are so scary!
Yeah, they are scary, but I think they’re also cool!