Brooklyn is one of New York City's five boroughs,
and is located on the western end of Long Island.
A "borough" is just a word for a section of the city.
Brooklyn has a population of nearly 2.6 million people.
Most of those people are hipsters and live in neighbourhoods called Williamsburg and Park Slope.
Many of Zach's friends want to create their own art.
Erin, his girlfriend, wants to publish a book of poetry or a novel.
"Where should we eat tonight, Zach?" Erin asks.
She's wearing a long, floral dress that looks like it came from Little House on the Prairie.
"There's a little gastropub a block away that I've been wanting to try.
I hear the tables were engineered from old barn doors."
"Gastropub" is simply another word for "restaurant."
"I'm not really in the mood for monkfish and arugala and kale," Zach says.
When he lived in Lansing he used to eat things like hamburgers and pizza.
"Can we just order in?"
"Of course not!" Erin says.
She tosses Zach his distressed Red Wing boots.
She makes a comment about how the boots were made for walking,
which is a reference that Zach gets immediately because when you're a hipster you get references to songs.
There is a ton of pedestrian traffic in Brooklyn.
Zach feels like he spends most of his time walking or sitting on a train or trying to park a car.
It leaves him very little time for writing.
Zach and Erin both went to the same small, liberal-arts college in Michigan.
Zach was in a band called "Couch" whose claim to fame is that they once played in their school cafeteria.
Zach had 500 copies of Couch's debut CD made – 455 of which still reside in his apartment.
Erin double-majored in Environmental Science and Literature,
meaning that she spent a lot of time reading Wendell Berry essays and poems.
They bonded over their shared love of being too clever for everybody else.