Hello, this is Susan speaking. May I speak to Miss Lee?
Hello Susan, this is Miss Lee.
Hello Miss Lee, I can't come to school today.
What's the matter?
I have a cold and a fever.
I'm sorry to hear that. Take care Susan.
Thank you Miss Lee.
Hello, this is Miss Lee speaking.
Hello, Miss Lee, this is Susan.
How are you now?
I'm fine, thank you.
Great! Can you come to school tomorrow?
Yes I can.
See you tomorrow Susan.
See you, Miss Lee.
Hello this is Sam speaking, may I speak to Lily?
Hello Sam, this is Lilly, how are you?
Not so good. I have a cough and a headache.
Hello, this is Mike speaking, may I speak to Sam?
Hello Mike, this is Sam, how are you?
Not bad, thank you.
Hello, this is Bobby speaking.
Hello Bobby.
Hi Tina, is Mary there?
No, she's at school.
Hello, this is Bobby speaking.
Hello Bobby.
Hi, Miss Lee, is Mr. Lee there?
No, he's at work.