You’re Going to Die!
Read the passage and answer this question: Will Mrs. Brown die in a month?
Mrs. Brown is a rich woman in the village.
She has four shops and a big farm.
She likes eating. But she doesn’t like sports or housework.
In the morning, Mrs. Brown often goes shopping and drinks coffee with friends.
In the evening she watches TV and goes to bed late at night.
What’s the matter?
I feel tired every day.
I’m worried because I’m too fat now!
I’m sorry, madam. You are going to die in a month!
Mrs. Brown is very sad. She doesn’t eat or drink.
She cries and cries: “ Oh, my god, I’m going to die…”
She can’t sleep well at night.
You see,doctor! I didn’t die.
Yes, madam.
Doctor! You’re wrong!
But look at you! Aren’t you thinner now?