tidy
整洁的
mess
脏乱
let
让
sock
短袜
yours
你（们）的
cap
帽子
mine
我的
crayon
蜡笔
umbrella
雨伞
nail
钉子
drop
落下
stick
粘贴
second
秒
hers
她的
theirs
他们的  她们的  它们的
tidy up
把  整理好
be full of
充满
a few
一些
Listen and say
听和说
-Are they yours? -No, they aren't.
-它们是你的吗  -不  他们不是
Look at your bedroom. What a mess!
看看你的卧室  太乱了
Let's tidy it up.
让我们把它打扫干净
Sure, Sally.
好的  萨利
Whose socks are those? Are they yours, Peter?
那些袜子是谁的  是你的吗  彼得
No, they aren't. They're Paul's.
不  不是  它们是保罗的
Can you put them on his bed?
你能把它们放在他的床上吗
Sure.
当然
Whose cap is this?
这是谁的帽子
It's mine.
这是我的
There's a T-shirt. Is this yours too, Peter?
这里有一件T恤 这是你的吗 彼得
No, it's Paul's.
不  这是彼得的
Can you put it on his bed?
你能把它放在他的床上吗
Sure.
当然
The room is now clean and tidy. Thank you for your help sally.
房间现在很整洁谢谢你的帮助  莎莉
You're welcome, Peter.
不客气  彼得